efxnews.com 2018-01-21

# Privacy Policy

This privacy statement covers eFXnews and its subsidiaries  

****Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access****

End User can access eFXnews' website home page and browse eFXnews' site without disclosing personal data.

****The Services and Links of our Website****

eFXnews' website does not enable visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.

eFXnews contains links to other sites. Please be aware that eFXnews is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. eFXnews encourages its users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by eFXnews.

**Automatic Collection of Information**

eFXnews does not automatically log personal data nor is information linked automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.

eFXnews uses internet protocol (IP) addresses to, inter alia, administer the site. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**

eFXnews collects personal Information that End User voluntarily provide when he/she uses or subscribes to any eFXnews service. eFXnews collects information that is necessary only to process End User's subscription.

eFXnews does not collect information about visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

If eFXnews wishes to use any personal data for a new purpose, End User is offered  the means to consent to this new purpose.

eFXnews only identifies an End User via cookies coming from a partnering website and who choses to subscribe to a subscription service. 

**Collection of Personal Financial Information by a Payment Service  **

eFXnews uses an unaffiliated payment service to allow End-user to subscribe to eFXnews paid service (eFXplus). If End-user wishes to subscribe or make a payment via credit card or PayPal, any information provided will be entered on a secure (SSL) and directed to eFXnews’ payment service provider. 

Any End-user information provided will be subject to the applicable Payment Terms and conditions in addition to this Privacy Policy. eFXnews has no control over, and is not responsible for, any payment service’s use of collected information.

All credit card and PayPal orders are processed through PayPal. The respective payment information collected on this website is stored on PayPal’s secure site and only an incomplete version of the payment information is accessible eFXnews to protect eFXnews’ End-user privacy.

End-user complete payment information collected for PayPal’s secure online payment system is governed by the [PayPal Privacy Policy](http://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full). The information is used by PayPal for billing purposes and to process your subscription.

All Skrill orders are processed off-site. eFXnews only has access to End-users Skrill account name and selected billing country.

The detailed information that remains accessible to eFXnews is outlines in eFXplus' [End User License Agreement](https://plus.efxnews.com/app.php/login?page=eula).

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice**

eFXnews does not disclose End User personal data to its subsidiaries or other organizations.

**Confidentiality / Security**

eFXnews works to protect the security of End User's information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the provided information.

eFXnews has implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that is under its control from:

  * unauthorized access 
  * improper use or disclosure 
  * unauthorized modification 
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All of eFXnews' employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of eFXnews' visitors' personal data.

eFXnews ensures that End User personal data is  not disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

**Cookies**

eFXnews may use cookies in order to customize this site for return visitors. These cookies are not required for site functionality. End User is not required to accept any cookies to use this site. eFXnews uses a tool called “ _Google Analytics_ ” to collect information about the use of this site. _Google Analytics_ collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. eFXnews uses the information it receives from _Google Analytics_  to improve this site and to provide to advertising agencies upon request. _Google Analytics_ collects only the IP address assigned to End User on the date he/she visited this site, rather than the name or other identifying information. eFXnews does not combine the information collected through the use of _Google Analytics_ with personally identifiable information. Although _Google Analytics_ plants a permanent cookie on End User's web browser to identify him/her as a unique user the next time he/she visits this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by _Google Analytics_ about End User's visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). End User can prevent _Google Analytics_ from recognizing him/her on return visits to this site by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on the browser.

**Policy Modification**

When eFXnews makes any material change to this Privacy Policy, the date on the bottom of this page will be changed, reflecting when the policy was last updated.
